<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>supakeen - life</title><link href="https://supakeen.com/weblog/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://supakeen.com/weblog/feeds/life.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://supakeen.com/weblog/</id><updated>2020-01-12T12:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>The plans for 2020</title><link href="https://supakeen.com/weblog/stuff-for-2020.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-01-12T12:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-01-12T12:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>supakeen</name></author><id>tag:supakeen.com,2020-01-12:/weblog/stuff-for-2020.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;Stuff I'll be working on in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Not quite the blog post I'd normally write. This one is mostly for me to have
a look at every now and then and see if I'm achieving what I want to do. A
very long New Years resolution!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For 2020 I'd like to extend the &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com"&gt;supakeen.com&lt;/a&gt; domain quite a bit. Fashioning
it like the olden homepages back when not everything was hosted on social
networks and the like. I'll be adding my &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/notes"&gt;notes&lt;/a&gt; on technical things and a
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/recipes"&gt;recipes&lt;/a&gt; section to this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I also build the &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/project/gb"&gt;gb&lt;/a&gt; project I've decided to make all this content
available over Gopher as well. That'll make sure I have to keep working on
making &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/project/gb"&gt;gb&lt;/a&gt; the best gopher server out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from that I'm looking into setting up a small FTP server as well where
my content can be downloaded. In case you want to archive this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/project/pinnwand"&gt;pinnwand&lt;/a&gt; you'll see the biggest changes in the shortest amount of time. A
branch containing multi-file pastes is almost ready to go. This will allow
users to paste multiple files in one go through the web interface or API if
they want. There will probably be room to create a small &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/project/pinnwand"&gt;pinnwand&lt;/a&gt; client
project if I can think of a good name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://supakeen.com/project/unchaind"&gt;unchaind&lt;/a&gt; project will stay dead as I no longer play the game. I'm thinking
of archiving it but I'll have to talk to other contributors first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it for 2020, keeping the plans small means they're hopefully more
achievable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A stretch goal would be to add a book review section, as if!&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="life"></category><category term="life"></category></entry></feed>